<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Classic</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Classic</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2018 21:51:21 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>455 Days</title>
      <link>/post/2018/11/05/455-days/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2018 21:51:21 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2018/11/05/455-days/</guid>
      <description>455 days ago today I started work at a fairly large medical software company in Madison, Wisconsin. About 3 weeks in I realized I didn&amp;rsquo;t want to be there1 very long.
Anyway its 1am now, maybe day 456 will be better.
 There? Here? Hard to say which is right but I&amp;rsquo;m still here as of today. !   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>/post/2018/11/04/about-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Nov 2018 21:57:38 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2018/11/04/about-me/</guid>
      <description>#This is who I am:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hacker with Bullhorn</title>
      <link>/post/2012/04/23/hacker-with-horn/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2012/04/23/hacker-with-horn/</guid>
      <description>Hacker with bullhorn: &amp;ldquo;Save your money! Accept one of our free tanks! It is invulnerable, and can drive across rocks and swamps at ninety miles an hour while getting a hundred miles to the gallon!&amp;rdquo;
Prospective station wagon buyer: &amp;ldquo;I know what you say is true&amp;hellip;but&amp;hellip;er&amp;hellip;I don&amp;rsquo;t know how to maintain a tank!&amp;rdquo;
Bullhorn: &amp;ldquo;You don&amp;rsquo;t know how to maintain a station wagon either!&amp;rdquo;
Buyer: &amp;ldquo;But this dealership has mechanics on staff.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Command Line Awesomeness</title>
      <link>/post/2012/03/12/command-line-awesomeness/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Mar 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2012/03/12/command-line-awesomeness/</guid>
      <description>This crud is called HTML (HyperText Markup Language) and it is basically a very simple programming language instructing your web browser how to draw a page on a screen. Anyone can learn HTML and many people do. The important thing is that no matter what splendid multimedia web pages they might represent, HTML files are just telegrams.
 When Ronald Reagan was a radio announcer, he used to call baseball games by reading the terse descriptions that trickled in over the telegraph wire and were printed out on a paper tape.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Markdown Guide</title>
      <link>/post/1/01/01/markdown-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/1/01/01/markdown-guide/</guid>
      <description>An h1 header Paragraphs are separated by a blank line.
2nd paragraph. Italic, bold, and monospace. Itemized lists look like:
 this one that one the other one  Note that &amp;mdash; not considering the asterisk &amp;mdash; the actual text content starts at 4-columns in.
 Block quotes are written like so.
They can span multiple paragraphs, if you like.
 Use 3 dashes for an em-dash. Use 2 dashes for ranges (ex.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>